ninjaloader.com 2014-04-01

# Ninjaloader - download your favorite media from YouTube - Privacy Policy

GigaClicks LP. (“GigaClicks”) takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about GigaClicks LP’s Privacy Policy (“Policy”). This Policy details how GigaClicks LP receives, collects and uses information in connection with your visit to its website accessed at www.ninjasurf.net or gigaclicks.net (“Website”) and through Your use of the NinjaSurf software (“Software”). 

#### 1\. Website Visitors: Collection and Use of Your Information

**Information You Provide:**  
Except as explicitly described below, you can use the Website and access the Software (collectively, “Service”) without providing any personally identifying information such as names, email addresses, and phone numbers (“Personal Information”). 

**Information We Automatically Collect:**  
GigaClicks LP does not automatically collect any Personal Information on or through the Website, except as may be provided by you in connection with your voluntary communications with GigaClicks LP. However, when you visit the Website, GigaClicks LP may automatically collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use of the Website. For example, GigaClicks LP may use “cookies”, “web beacons” and similar devices to track your activities as a visitor to the Website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record- keeping purposes. A web-beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at the Website. Cookies may be used to analyze Website usage, improve content, customize the Website’s content and layout and for other customer service purposes. GigaClicks LP’s use of cookies or similar devices is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

When you visit the Website, GigaClicks LP may also automatically receive and record certain other non- personally identifiable information of the type that servers typically collect on webserver logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpages that you visit. GigaClicks LP collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the Website, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. GigaClicks LP will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with the aggregate data of its users. Please be aware that some non-personally identifiable information such as Uniform Resource Locators (“URL’s”) or Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses could become Personal Information when combined by third parties with the ISP’s records. GigaClicks LP does NOT do this with your information. 

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**  
GigaClicks LP does not rent, sell, or share any information about you with any third-parties. GigaClicks LP may disclose your information if GigaClicks LP believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of GigaClicks LP (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of GigaClicks LP services or members of the public.

GigaClicks LP may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help it provide, analyze and improve the Website (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, information processing and improvement of the Website’s features and services). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on behalf of GigaClicks LP and under obligations similar to those in this Policy. 

**Third party advertisers and websites**  
If you access another website through the Website and that website is operated by any entity other than GigaClicks LP, that site is referred to as a “Third Party Site”. Unless GigaClicks LP clearly indicates otherwise at the time of collection, GigaClicks LP does not share Personal Information with Third Party Sites. Please be aware however that these Third Party Sites may collect information about you. Please see the Third Party Site’s privacy policy to better understand what information is collected, how it is used and shared, and your choices regarding control. GigaClicks LP has no control over these linked Third Party Sites, each of which has a separate privacy and data collection practice, independent of this Policy. GigaClicks LP does not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any Third Party Site. As such, GigaClicks LP is not responsible for, nor have control over, the content or the privacy policies of these Third Party Sites. You must read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit when linking from the Website. This Policy applies solely to information collected by GigaClicks LP. 

#### 2\. NinjaSurf: Collection and Use of Your Information

**Information GigaClicks LP receives when NinjaSurf runs on your computer.**  
You do not need to provide any Personal Information in order to download or use the Software.

When NinjaSurf runs on your computer, GigaClicks LP may automatically receive non- personally identifiable information, such as your system’s IP address, when you contact our servers. NinjaSurf itself does not set any cookies. 

**Information NinjaSurf sends to websites and ISP’s**  
Like most web browsers, the websites that is automatically visited using the NinjaSurf will receive certain non- personally identifiable information, for example, this information may consist of the type of browser, type of device, and your IP address. These sites may also set their own cookies or other website data on your system. Each website determines its own privacy practices and is not controlled or monitored by GigaClicks LP. If you want to understand how these websites use your information, you must review that particular website’s privacy policy. All stored data will be automatically deleted after NinjaSurf session ends. 

**Information GigaClicks LP Stores when NinjaSurf runs.**  
NinjaSurf stores some of your information locally on your system. For example, the NinjaSurf may store basic browsing history such as URL’s of pages is visited by NinjaSurf, text and images from those pages, IP addresses linked from the pages, index of most pages you visit, cookies deposited on your system by and a record of downloads you have made. All stored data will be automatically deleted after NinjaSurf session ends. Also, NinjaSurf will put unique identifier to your computer in order to track further NinjaSurf sessions. 

#### 3\. Additional Privacy Information for the Website and NinjaSurf

**Children’s Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. GigaClicks LP operates its Website and Software in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The Website and Software are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that such individuals do not provide any personally indentifying information through the Website. 

**Security**  
GigaClicks LP takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although GigaClicks LP cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE WEBSITE FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICES, WHICH ARE GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS POLICY, AND GIGACLICKS LP’S TERMS OF USE, YOU ARE NOT TRANSFERRING ANY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES. ADDITIONALLY, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO AND PROCESSED IN COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR COUNTRY. 

**Data Retention**  
GigaClicks LP will retain your information for only as long as needed to provide you services and fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy. GigaClicks LP may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with its legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce its agreements. Consistent with these requirements, GigaClicks LP will try to delete your information as quickly as possible. 

**Business Transitions**  
In the event that GigaClicks LP goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Information will likely be among the assets transferred. GigaClicks LP will post a notice on this Website of any such change in ownership or control of the Information GigaClicks LP may have prior to such transfer. 

**Changes to Policy**  
From time to time, GigaClicks LP may revise this Policy. GigaClicks LP will post the revised Policy on the Website, so that users can always be aware of what information GigaClicks LP collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. GigaClicks LP will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, GigaClicks LP will provide more prominent notice. You should also visit this page periodically to review any changes to this Policy.
